Just when you thought it was safe to dig in the toy box!
Doll Shark is a horror, comedy film directed by Mark Polonia.
A child's stuffed toy shark comes to life and goes on a killing spree.
Lyla, played by Danielle Donahue.
Shark Tale is a 2004 American animated adventure film directed by Vicky Jenson, Bibo Bergeron, and Rob
Letterman (in his feature length directorial debut), and written by Letterman and Michael J.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation, the film features the voices of Will Smith, Robert De
Niro, Renée Zellweger, Angelina Jolie, Jack Black, and Martin Scorsese.
It follows an underachieving fish named Oscar (Smith) who falsely claims to have killed the son of a
shark mob boss Don Lino (De Niro) in an attempt to advance his community standing.
Oscar teams up with the mobster's younger son
Lenny (Black) to keep up the facade.
Shark Tale premiered at the Venice Film Festival on September 10, 2004, and
was theatrically released in the United States on October 1.
It made $374.6 million worldwide against its $75 million budget, finishing
its theatrical run as the ninth-highest-grossing film of 2004.
The film received mixed reviews from critics; advocacy groups criticized
the film for its use of Italian-American stereotypes.
It was nominated for Best Animated Feature at the 77th Academy Awards.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.